02:50 Wait
a second, Adrian. We're coming out of executive session at 02:57.
So Amanda's in the waiting room. Do I let her back into the meeting?
Sure. Go ahead.
Everybody's
back in the meeting. So everybody in the waiting room is in? Yep.
Okay.
Are we ready?
>> Go ahead, Adrian. I'll make a motion that the board of selectmen will empower Dennis O'Brien to make a settlement
offer to
the employee that asked for a
settlement.
>> Someone want to second that?
I'll second it. Alright.
Further discussion?
All those in favor? Aye. Aye.
Okay. I know Paula may not be with us. So Yeah. We'll call Paula an abstention.
All right. Anything else?
Nope, we good? Nope. Someone want to make a motion to adjourn? Motion to adjourn at 02:58PM.
Second. Okay.
All those in favor? Aye.
>> Aye. That's
the only thing, Jeff, that Gretchen
asked for is if we can call out time when things are happening. That's all. That was probably our biggest thing. All right. No problem. I'll remember that. Thank you. So 259,
>> we're done.
Yep.
All right. Thank you. All right. We'll see you guys.